{"data":[{"question":"He had _______ money that he didn't know what to do with it.","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"such a ","d":"so much","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- \"So\" can be combined with \"much\" or \"little\" plus a non-countable noun to show extremes in amount. This form is often used in exclamations.\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She's very pretty. She's got _______ beautiful eyes.","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"such a ","d":"so much","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The heels of her shoes are _______ high that she looks much taller.","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"so much ","d":"such a","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The hall was _______ crowded that I couldn't find a seat.","a":"so much ","b":"so","c":"such ","d":"such a","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Those boys are ________ stupid!","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"such a ","d":"so a","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- So \/ Such in exclamations:\n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural)\n+ So + adjective\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"It was ________ interesting book.","a":"such ","b":"such an","c":"such a ","d":"so","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- So \/ Such in exclamations:\n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural)\n+ So + adjective\n-An + singular noun beginning with a vowel","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She was ________ silly girl.","a":"such ","b":"so","c":"such a ","d":"so much","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- So \/ Such in exclamations:\n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural)\n+ So + adjective\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"They had six children. They hadn't expected to have ________.","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"so many ","d":"so much","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- \"So\" can be combined with \"many\" or \"few\" plus a plural noun to show extremes in amount. This form is often used in exclamations.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Maggy was ________ nice everybody loved her.","a":"so ","b":"such","c":"so much ","d":"such a","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Such + a + (adjective) + singular noun (+ that + result)\n- Such + plural\/uncountable noun (+ that + result)\n- So + adjective\/adverb (+ that + result)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I haven't seen her for ________ long.","a":"as ","b":"such a","c":"so ","d":"such","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- So \/ Such in exclamations:\n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural)\n+ So + adjective\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"9","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}